# **ROHAN RAWAT**

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

9897644759 | rohan.rawat.9897@gmail.com | https://linkedin.com/in/rohannn | https://nnboru.github.io



# **PROFILE**

3+ years of experience with live agent support platform at Fareportal. Worked on microservice architecture using .NET, SQL Server, MongoDB, React along with generating daily reports and performing data analysis.

Skilled in designing highly complex workflows, handling dependencies and parallelizing workload for faster deliveries.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Software Developer, Fareportal Pvt. Ltd., Gurugram

Jul 2022 — Present

Product based B2C Flight booking company where I served as a full stack developer. Here our team worked on handling schedule change and cancellation on customer bookings. Worked with a dynamic fast pacing team on end-to-end flow automation and its fallback manual agent flow process, while maintaining reports and reviewing & debugging failure cases. For ~450 bookings received per day, we have achieved 94% adoption with 72% automation.

### Internship, APPNIVI IT Solution, Hyderabad

Jul 2019 — Aug 2019

Machine learning with Python □ Data cleansing, abstraction and graph plotting □ Implemented ML algorithms

#### **EDUCATION**

MTech (CSE Analytics) - NIT, Delhi - 8.46CGPA

Jul 2020 — Jun 2022

BTech (CSE) - GBPIET Pauri, Uttarakhand

Jul 2016 — Jun 2020

XII - Army Public School, Meerut Cantt

Mar 2014

#### **PROJECTS**

# Cattle Identification

MTech Thesis | ML Transfer learning | Python

Worked on a private dataset of cattle muzzle images for identification task and using it for designing a biometric recognition system.

#### MathBot [7]

BTech Final year project 2020 | Python Flask | SQLite | JS

A simple chatbot specifically designed for performing math related tasks like solve equation, draw graph, draw charts for csv file.

# Stone Paper Scissor 🔀 🌘



MERN | Socket.io

Create password protected private room and share link with others to play the game on each individual device online in real time. There is no limit on number of players and they can also chat within room while playing.

JavaScript Lightweight offline 2-4 player web game.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#, C++, Python, HTML, CSS, JS

Framework & libraries: .NET, nodejs, React, express, bootstrap, flask, Pygame, socket.io

Databases: SQL Server, MongoDB, Redis,

Tools: Azure, git, Postman, Kibana, Grafana, AppInsights, RabbitMQ

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Competitive programming

- Codechef 5 star www.codechef.com/users/Rohannn Codeforces max expert www.codeforces.com/profile/nnboru
- Participation in ICPC regionals 2019-2020, went till national round

**GATE 2020** - score 492